<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.2//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.2/docbookx.dtd">
<book id="diffusion" lang="en">

    <bookinfo>
        <title>Documentation for the diffusion module Version 1.1.0 (require docmanager module Version 1.1.0)</title>
        
        <author>
            <firstname>Jeff</firstname> 
            <surname>Saucier</surname>
            <affiliation>
                <address><email>jsaucier _AT_ infostrategique _DOT_ com</email></address>
            </affiliation>
        </author>
    </bookinfo>

    <chapter id="changelog">
        <title>ChangeLog</title>
        
        <para>I recommend to update to this new version. Just overwrite the old files with the new one (pay attention to "include/configs.php" !!)</para>
        
        <para>Here is what change since the last version :</para>
        <itemizedlist>
            <listitem><para>Now require and use docmanager Version 1.1.0</para></listitem>
            <listitem><para>Bugs correction</para></listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
    </chapter>
    
    <chapter id="informations">
        <title>Informations</title>
        
        <para>This module allow you to send email with files to the users of your site. This module is not very usable "as is" because it is very tied to the CRISP's extranet. But, you can adapt it easily for your needs.</para>
        
        <para>This is what the module provide :</para>
        <itemizedlist>
            <listitem><para>Sending email to peoples of the Members group or all users</para></listitem>
            <listitem><para>Send a copy in the forums for archive to allow discussion</para></listitem>
            <listitem><para>Put the attached files in the document center for allowing peoples that receive the email to download the files</para></listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
        
        <para>This module has been developped for the CRISP extranet and is released with the GPL license.</para>
    </chapter>
    
    <chapter id="installation">
        <title>Installation</title>

        <section id="requirements">
            <title>Requirements</title>
            
            <para>This module has been tested with the following configurations. It may work on other plateforme and configurations :</para>
            
            <itemizedlist>
                <listitem><para>NOTE : This module is not very usable "as is" because it is very tied to the CRISP's extranet. But, you can adapt it easily for your needs.</para></listitem>
                <listitem><para>NOTE : This module depend of our other module, docmanager Version 1.1.0. You must have it in order to make this one work.</para></listitem>
                <listitem><para>Xoops 2.0.7.x and 2.0.9.x</para></listitem>
                <listitem><para>Linux and Apache</para></listitem>
            </itemizedlist>            
        </section>
        
        <section id="mod_installation">
            <title>Module installation</title>
            
            <para>To install this module, first untar or unzip it. It will create a folder named "diffusion".</para>
            <para>Copy this folder to the Xoops modules folder and activate the new module from the administration page.</para>
            <para>Now, you must create a folder in the docmanager module. I recommend to create it on the Root folder and hide it so nobody will see it except admin. Adjust the permissions for every group to access it (they can't access the folder directly because it's hidden but can access file in it with a link)</para>
            <para>After you have created the hidden folder, note the folder id and put it in include/configs.php in the diffusion module.</para>
            <para>The next step is to create to forum categories, one for member users and one for all users. Put the respective forums id in include/configs.php.</para>
            <para>In include/configs.php, you can also specify the maximum number of files you want when sending an email.</para>
        </section>
    </chapter>
</book>
